luulla.com 2013-08-23

# Luulla - an online marketplace to buy and sell unique products, fashion, handmade and supplies

protecting personal information

-

At Luulla, our priority is to protect the personal information that you have provided to us in a safe and efficient way. We only collect information from you whenever it's necessary and there is certain information that you can choose not to provide or may hde its access from others through the privacy settings at your account.

disclosure of information

-

Luulla will not sell or disclose your name or email address to any third parties without your explicit consent except as specified in this privacy policy.

visibility of information

-

You can browse www.luulla.com without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. However, if you choose to register, you are no longer anonymous to us. If you choose to use our service, we may require that you provide your contact, identity, financial and other personal information as indicated by the forms on this site.

buying and selling

-

If you choose to buy and sell on www.luulla.com, we collect information about your buying and selling behavior. We also collect information related to feedbacks from both the buyer and seller of the store whenever a transaction occurs.

selling

-

If you are a seller, we collect additional information such as your billing address, phone number, PayPal account username, geographical location, shipping address, credit card number and its expiration date.

posting content

-

If you choose to post content on www.luulla.com, such as comments on streams, forums or product items, list, dashboard, chat rooms, we will collect and store this information

cookies

-

Luulla uses cookies at certain pages of the site. 'Cookies' is a small file stored at your hard drive that will help us identify you whenever you signed in or added an item to the shopping cart. By using cookies, it allows us to better customized the user experience and also promote safer trading.

disabling cookies

-

There are certain features that require the use of 'cookies' to function. You may decline the user of 'cookies' using the browser settings, and if you do so, there arecertain features on www.luulla.com that will not function. By not allowing 'session-cookies', you might not be able to sign in to your account. There are also certain 'cookies' that are used to keep track of the activity of your shopping cart. By disabling 'cookies', you will not be able to complete a purchase or transaction.
